PABLO POCOSTALES

Videographer // Video editor

ABOUT ME

I consider myself a professional filmmaker with extensive experience in camera operation, sound equipment, and scene lighting. I completed my studies in 2012, and since then, I have been continuously specializing and furthering my education in the audiovisual field up to the present day.

PORTFOLIO

pablopocostales.com/

flickr.com/people/pocostales/

CONTACT ME

Howald, Luxembourg

+34 654 70 97 32 pocostales7@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

Spanish

Native

English

Advanced level

German

Basic level

EXPERIENCE

Nov 2018 - present	VIDEOGRAPHER & MULTIMEDIA DESIGNER Deloitte // Luxembourg		
	Video filming and editing for the branding department. Creation of motion design and promotional videos for social medial.		
Apr 2017 - Nov 2018	VIDEOGRAPHER & GRAPHIC DESIGNER Freelancer // Spain		
	Video creation and editing, logo design a catalog layout for web pagination, and so		
Mar 2013	CAMERAMAN & VIDEO EDIT	CAMERAMAN & VIDEO EDITOR	
- Apr 2016	Alcor Extremadura Raid // Spain		
	Recording and editing of promotional vio	deos for social networks.	
Nov 2011 - Mar 2012	VIDEOGRAPHER & PRODUCTION		
	MediaUni Web - UV // Spain		
	Cameraman, video editor, developer and creator of a Sport program for the official webpage of University of Valencia.		
Jul 2011 - Sept 2011	CAMERA ASSISTANT		
	VAV Productions // Spain	VAV Productions // Spain	
	Camera assistant in a live program of Canal Extremadura TV.		
EDUCATION	NS —		
Nov 2011 - Jun 2012	MASTER'S DEGREE IN AUDIOVISUALS CONTENTSAND FORMATS University of Valencia		
Sept 2007 - Sept 2011	BACHELOR OF AUDIOVISUAL COMMUNICATION University of Extremadura		
VOLUNTAR	Y WORKS		
2016	CZECH REPUBLIC Training course video editing		
2015	NORTH MACEDONIA EuroHandball Woman Sub17 as a cameraman and video editor		
2014	BULGARIA International Short Films Festival as a film assistant		
PRO SKILL	s -		
	Premiere Pro Pl	notoshop ———	
		ustrator <u> </u>	
	Adobe Audition In	Design	

DaVinci Resolve =

Firefly